One night is all that stands between them and freedom.
But it's going to be one hell of a night.
From Dusk Till Dawn is a horror, action, thriller
film directed by Robert Rodriguez.
After kidnapping a father and his two kids, the Gecko brothers head south to a seedy
Mexican bar to hide out in safety, unaware of its notorious vampire clientele.
Seth Gecko, played by George Clooney.
Richard Gecko, played by Quentin Tarantino.
Jacob Fuller, played by Harvey Keitel.
Kate Fuller, played by Juliette Lewis.
Scott Fuller, played by Ernest Liu.
Santanico Pandemonium, played by Salma Hayek Pinault.
From Dusk till Dawn is a 1996 American crime action-horror film directed by Robert Rodriguez
and written by Quentin Tarantino from a concept and story by Robert Kurtzman.
Starring Harvey Keitel, George Clooney, Tarantino, Ernest Liu, and Juliette Lewis, the plot follows a pair of American criminal brothers (Clooney and Tarantino), who take a
family as hostages (Keitel, Liu and Lewis) to cross into Mexico, but ultimately find themselves trapped in a saloon, defending against an even greater threat.
From Dusk till Dawn premiered on January 17, 1996, at the Cinerama Dome theater in
Hollywood, Los Angeles, and was released on January 19 in the United States.
It initially received mixed reviews from critics, who
described the film as well-made if overly violent.
After enjoying financial success at the box office, From Dusk till Dawn has since become a cult film and
spawned a media franchise of sequel films, a video game, and other media adaptations.
The film explores themes of dancing, showdown,
sheriff, sibling relationship, vampire.
The tone is dark and intense.